<resources>
    <string name="app_name">USB-Tour Team6</string>
    <string name="get_directions">Get Directions</string>
    <string name="show_on_map">Show on Map</string>
    <string name="search_title">Search&#8230;</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search&#8230;</string>



    <!--Fixing warnings-->
    <string name="Find_Room_USB">Find A Room in the USB</string>



    <!--Needed for nav drawer etc-->
    <string name="title_activity_nav_bar">NavBar</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>


    <!--building info Strings | Remaining strings start-->
    <string name="tour_guide">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="bus_info">By Bus: Barrack Road, St James Park</string>
    <string name="metro_info">By Metro: St James Park</string>
    <string name="nearby_transport_links">Nearby Transport Links</string>
    <string name="cafe">Eat@Urban - Cafe</string>
    <string name="contact_info_button">Contact Information</string>
    <string name="opening_hours_button">Opening Hours</string>
    <string name="general_info">General Information</string>
    <!--End-->

    <!--get directions Strings | Remaining strings start-->
    <string name="stairs">Stairs</string>
    <string name="elevator">Elevator</string>
    <!--End-->

    <!--level x Strings | Remaining strings start-->
    <string name="tutor_rooms">Tutor Rooms</string>
    <string name="show_more">Show more&#8230;</string>
    <string name="study_spaces">Study Spaces</string>
    <string name="other_rooms">Other rooms</string>
    <!--End-->

    <!--level x Strings | Remaining strings start-->
    <string name="tutor_rooms">Tutor Rooms</string>
    
    <!--End-->

    <!--Opening hours-->
    <string name="opening_hours">
        <b>Monday - Friday:</b> 06:00 - 23:00\n\n
        <b>Saturday - Sunday:</b> 12:00 - 21:00
    </string>

    <!--Contact information-->
    <string name="contact_info">
        <b>Telephone:</b>\n\t\t0191 208 7972\n\n
        <b>Address:</b>\n\t\tSchool Of Computing\n
        \t\tUrban Sciences Building\n
        \t\tNewcastle University\n
        \t\t1 Science Square\n
        \t\tNewcastle Helix\n
        \t\tNewcastle Upon Tyne\n
        \t\tNE4 5TG
    </string>

    <!--Cafe information-->
    <string name="cafe_info">
        The perfect space to refuel, whether it’s a formal meeting or a relaxing break, with a choice of barista coffee, deli sandwiches, paninis, jacket potatoes or snacks.
        \n\nIt is open to staff, students and the general public from <b>8am to 4pm </b>on a daily basis in term time.
    </string>

    <!--Application Information-->
    <string name="app_info">
        <b>Application name:</b> \n\t\tUSB Tour Guide\n\n
        <b>Running on:</b> \n\t\tAndroid 5.0 Lollipop and above\n\n
        <b>Version:</b> \n\t\t1.0
    </string>

    <!--Tour guide text-->

    <string name="groundFloorTourTitle">
        Cyber Physical Systems Laboratory
    </string>
    <string name="groundFloorTourText">
    This laboratory focuses on systems that combine hardware, software, networking and control. Research enables modules to be co-developed and co-simulated by joining them together to enhance product performance and optimisation.
        \nIt is currently developing integrated systems for transport, smart grids, building infrastructure, etc.
    </string>
    <string name="firstFloorTourTitle">
        Open Lab
    </string>
    <string name="firstFloorTourText">
    Open Lab is focused on human interaction with computers and human-based design of computer systems. Many members of this group originate in disciplines outside computer science, including psychology, electronic engineering, clinical sciences, education, design and fine art.
    \n\nOne of the examples of projects in the Open Lab is the ambient kitchen. This has utensils that contain instruments that communicate with the network around them allowing the kitchen to help you work out if you are stirring, cutting, how long you have been doing it for, etc. This technology might allow someone with mild dementia to get help in the kitchen and enable them to get computer aided assistance to lead a more independent life.
    \n\nOpen Lab also houses the EPSRC-funded Doctoral Training Centre for Digital Civics.\n
    </string>
    <string name="firstFloorTourTitle2">
        Lecture Theatre
    </string>
    <string name="firstFloorTourText2">
        The Lecture Theatre has a capacity of 303 students and has the ability for the lecturer to customise what is shown on each of the projected screens. This means the lecturer can still display the lecture notes whilst they are demonstrating a piece of code or practical element of the future.
    \n\nThere is a power socket at every seat and each seat has lumbar support.
    </string>
    <string name="secondFloorTourTitle">
        Reception / School Office
    </string>
    <string name="secondFloorTourText">
    The School Office contains all the Professional Services staff and the NUIT Computing Support
    team. This is the area where you should come and ask for help and support when required.\n
    </string>
    <string name="secondFloorTourTitle2">
        Teaching Innovation Group (TIG)
    </string>
    <string name="secondFloorTourText2">
        The Teaching Innovation Group aims to encourage, foster and pursue innovation in teaching. TIG
    run the Outreach Programme with the Computing at School initiative.
        \n\nThis programme runs teacher
    training, outreach events and visits to schools.
        \n\nTIG are also responsible for reviewing existing
    degree programmes, developing employability skills and maintaining industry links.
    </string>

    <string name="thirdFloorTourTitle">
        Flat Floor Teaching
    </string>
    <string name="thirdFloorTourText">
    There are 312 Machines on the third floor, with all the software that students will need for their degree. The machines run
    NetSupport software that allows the lecturer to send and receive files from the class. The
    lecturer is also able to share their screen to the students and give a lecture.
    </string>

    <string name="fifthFloorTourTitle">
        ICOS
    </string>
    <string name="fifthFloorTourText">Interdisciplinary Computing and Complex BioSystems (ICOS).\n
    The ICOS team have expertise in machine intelligence, complex systems and biocomputing. The
    problems they focus on are natural complex systems and synthetic ones. This ranges from biology,
    chemistry and physics, to biological engineering, healthcare and software engineering.</string>

    <string name="sixthFloorTourTitle">
        Secure and Resilient Systems (SRS)
    </string>
    <string name="sixthFloorTourText">
    The SRS group’s research directly contributes to creating modern information systems, networks
    and infrastructures.
        \n\nThe SRS group investigates fundamental concepts, development techniques,
    models, architectures and mechanisms that directly contribute to making modern information
    systems, networks and infrastructures that are secure in all aspects. Such systems need to be
    resilient to malicious attacks and accidental faults to deliver services that can be justifiably
    trusted by their stakeholders.
        \n\nThe Academic Centre for Excellence in Cyber Security Research is
    also located here.</string>

    <string-array name="floors">
        <item>Ground Floor</item>
        <item>First Floor</item>
        <item>Second Floor</item>
        <item>Third Floor</item>
        <item>Fourth Floor</item>
        <item>Fifth Floor</item>
        <item>Sixth Floor</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--Developer Information-->
    <string name="developer_info">This application was developed by Team 6 at
        Newcastle University by Stage 2 students in 2018/19\n\n
        <b>The Team:</b>\n
        \t\tT. Alvikas:\n
        \t\t\t- Lead Tester \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Web Developer \n\n

        \t\tW. G. Comber: \n
        \t\t\t- Team Leader \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Tester \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Documenter \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Programmer \n\n

        \t\tO. J. E Gilley: \n
        \t\t\t- Lead Web Developer \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Programmer \n\n

        \t\tE. J. Goodchild: \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Programmer \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Documenter \n\n

        \t\tJ. P. Lawrence: \n
        \t\t\t- Lead Programmer \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Web Developer \n\n

        \t\tJ. E. P. Lowthian: \n
        \t\t\t- Lead Designer \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Programmer \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Documenter \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Researcher \n\n

        \t\tI. J. Mohammed: \n
        \t\t\t- Lead Administrator \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Programmer \n\n

        \t\tJ. E. O’Connor: \n
        \t\t\t- Lead Researcher \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Designer \n\n

        \t\tE. R. G. R Phillips: \n
        \t\t\t- Lead Documenter \n
        \t\t\t- Junior Tester \n\n
    </string>

</resources>
